Kettle and Idol
All right, let's go ahead and check the business cards. Let's go ahead and check the business cards.
Please give the title call to ℃-ute.
My Three Elements
Okay, so, this is the "Three Elements of Myself.
We are going to ask you to introduce three elements that affirm you.
Is three okay?
I have narrowed it down to three.
Have you narrowed it down to three?
I have four elements that I'm not sure about.
So you've narrowed it down to four.
Can you say four?
Four?
Concern 1 for Noborufuku.
Concern 1 for Shofuku.
Haul trouble.
It's on the both south lines.
It's right there.
This is my favorite scene.
Let's start there.
Yagami, you're the third generation, so I've narrowed it down to three.
What's wrong with that?
Are you trying to be mean?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but you're accompanied by a plum dunk.
I'd like to talk about the element of insecurity of Shofuku.
Anzai-sensei...
I'm a little bit worried about that, too.
Yes.
Let's leave it at that.
Thank you very much.
Please tell us about the next Nippon element.
Ta-da!
1. cartoon animation
Sleep
3. a girl in a box3. a girl in a box
Next time preview
Please tell us about the Nippon element of anime.
Manga anime. I have been watching manga anime since I was a child,
As for manga, I still read Summon! I read Shonen Jump every week.
I love it that much.
And as for anime, I love Conan,
I love Conan so much that I started writing a blog called Detective Pearl,
I love Conan so much that I started a blog called Detective Pearl, which you should definitely check out.
Why are you smiling?
I thought that's right, and there was a Sambo at the top of my head saying to check it out first,
I thought you were into it.
It's a laugh of interest.
A laugh of interest? I'm glad.
So, you're saying that the majority of your manga are from the JUMP series?
Yes, that's right. I like shonen manga,
I like the Jump series.
You have been reading manga since you were a child,
Is there anything that inspired you to read manga?
My parents had a lot of manga at home,
My parents had a lot of manga at home, and they told me to read Slam Dunk, so I did, and I was hooked.
Also, my father used to read Jump,
That's how I came to read it.
Do you remember the first manga you read?
And Slam Dunk?
Slam dunk?
Maybe.
But I also read glass screens.
What's wrong with different screens?
Should I say a different genre?
Oh, that one.
I also have candy canes at home.
Oh, my.
Are you still adding more and more manga?
Yes, I'm getting more and more.
Lately, the 12th round is very hot in my mind,Because the twelfth round has been hot in my mind lately,
I'm adding more of those things. By myself.
Do you feel like you are setting the stage for the rules?
Yes, I am.
Thank you very much.
Have you been reading JUMP recently?
Yes, I have.
There is always the 12th round.
Yes, but One Piece is also going well right now,
But I'm in a month-long relief period right now,
So I feel like I should look back on it.
Do you talk about manga with the members?
Yes, we do.
I like One Piece with Waka-chan,
With Waka,
There is a diagnostic test called "Zoro Noh" and "Sanji Noh,
We do that together.
I also talk about Gundam with Karen.
Can I make my next Gunpla?
Can I make Gunpla?
Karen has started building Gundam models.
I thought it was great when Tunic showed her his Gunpla.
I used to make them, so I was surprised.
I was surprised to hear that you started making Gunpla.
My favorite mobile suit is called Sinanju.
Oh, Sinanju.
I like it because it has a similar name.
What's the reason?
Which is it?
It's the Akadema with the old clothes Rontar is riding.
Yes, yes.
Because it has a feeling.
I'm having so much fun that for the first time I didn't get out that day.
Really, I'm the type of person who can sleep the day before a concert or at all.
This program is Mr. Shy Boy's one love.
Mahiyu-san.Mahiyuu-san
Mr. Kitakasa
Mr. Daisho
Mitsuru-san
Thank you very much for your support!
We wish you all the best for the future!